{
  "title": "韓国語単語②",
  "data": [
    {"question":"앞", "answer": ["前"]},
    {"question":"양말", "answer": ["靴下"]},
    {"question":"얼굴", "answer": ["顔"]},
    {"question":"여행", "answer": ["旅行"]},
    {"question":"영어", "answer": ["英語"]},
    {"question":"올해", "answer": ["今年"]},
    {"question":"외국", "answer": ["外国"]},
    {"question":"우체국", "answer": ["郵便局"]},
    {"question":"은행", "answer": ["銀行"]},
    {"question":"음악", "answer": ["音楽"]},
    {"question":"이름", "answer": ["名前"]},
    {"question":"자동차", "answer": ["自動車"]},
    {"question":"작년", "answer": ["去年"]},
    {"question":"정도", "answer": ["程度"]},
    {"question":"종이", "answer": ["紙"]},
    {"question":"지금", "answer": ["今"]},
    {"question":"지진", "answer": ["地震"]},
    {"question":"책", "answer": ["本"]},
    {"question":"취미", "answer": ["趣味"]},
    {"question":"코", "answer": ["鼻"]},
    {"question":"학생", "answer": ["学生"]},
    {"question":"허리", "answer": ["腰"]},
    {"question":"회사", "answer": ["会社"]},
    {"question":"가운데", "answer": ["真ん中"]},
    {"question":"거울", "answer": ["鏡"]},
    {"question":"건물", "answer": ["建物"]},
    {"question":"고양이", "answer": ["猫"]},
    {"question":"공원", "answer": ["公園"]},
    {"question":"과자", "answer": ["お菓子"]},
    {"question":"김", "answer": ["海苔"]},
    {"question":"야구", "answer": ["野球"]},
    {"question":"어제", "answer": ["昨日"]},
    {"question":"여름", "answer": ["夏"]},
    {"question":"역", "answer": ["駅"]},
    {"question":"영화", "answer": ["映画 "]},
    {"question":"옷", "answer": ["服"]},
    {"question":"우산", "answer": ["傘"]},
    {"question":"위", "answer": ["上"]},
    {"question":"음식", "answer": ["食べ物"]},
    {"question":"의사", "answer": ["医師"]},
    {"question":"일", "answer": ["仕事"]},
    {"question":"자리", "answer": ["席"]},
    {"question":"저녁", "answer": ["夕方"]},
    {"question":"제일", "answer": ["１番"]},
    {"question":"주말", "answer": ["週末"]},
    {"question":"집", "answer": ["家"]},
    {"question":"차", "answer": ["車・お茶"]},
    {"question":"처음", "answer": ["最初"]},
    {"question":"친구", "answer": ["友達"]},
    {"question":"편지", "answer": ["手紙"]},
    {"question":"해", "answer": ["太陽"]},
    {"question":"화장실", "answer": ["トイレ"]},
    {"question":"가수", "answer": ["歌手"]},
    {"question":"거리", "answer": ["距離"]},
    {"question":"거짓말", "answer": ["嘘"]},
    {"question":"계단", "answer": ["階段 "]},
    {"question":"고향", "answer": ["故鄉"]},
    {"question":"공항", "answer": ["空港"]},
    {"question":"근처", "answer": ["近所"]},
    {"question":"꿈", "answer": ["夢"]},
    {"question":"날짜", "answer": ["日"]},
    {"question":"내주", "answer": ["来週"]},
    {"question":"눈물", "answer": ["涙"]},
    {"question":"도시락", "answer": ["弁当"]},
    {"question":"동물", "answer": ["動物 "]},
    {"question":"마지막", "answer": ["最後"]},
    {"question":"맞은편", "answer": ["向かい側"]},
    {"question":"모자", "answer": ["帽子"]},
    {"question":"무릎", "answer": ["ひざ"]},
    {"question":"물건", "answer": ["物"]},
    {"question":"내용", "answer": ["内容"]},
    {"question":"냄새", "answer": ["におい"]},
    {"question":"담배", "answer": ["たばこ"]},
    {"question":"도장", "answer": ["はんこ"]},
    {"question":"땀", "answer": ["汗"]},
    {"question":"마찬가지", "answer": ["同じこと"]},
    {"question":"며칠", "answer": ["何日"]},
    {"question":"목소리", "answer": ["声"]},
    {"question":"문화", "answer": ["文化"]},
    {"question":"바람", "answer": ["風"]},
    {"question":"작다", "answer": ["小さい"]},
    {"question":"짧다", "answer": ["短い"]},
    {"question":"춥다", "answer": ["寒い"]},
    {"question":"가볍다", "answer": ["軽い"]},
    {"question":"기쁘다", "answer": ["嬉しい"]},
    {"question":"넓다", "answer": ["広い"]},
    {"question":"달다", "answer": ["甘い"]},
    {"question":"맵다", "answer": ["辛い"]},
    {"question":"바쁘다", "answer": ["忙しい"]},
    {"question":"비슷하다", "answer": ["似ている"]},
    {"question":"새롭다", "answer": ["新しい"]},
    {"question":"적다", "answer": ["少ない"]},
    {"question":"차다", "answer": ["冷たい"]},
    {"question":"크다", "answer": ["大きい"]},
    {"question":"강하다", "answer": ["強い"]},
    {"question":"깊다", "answer": ["深い"]},
    {"question":"다르다", "answer": ["違う"]},
    {"question":"따뜻하다", "answer": ["暖かい"]},
    {"question":"무겁다", "answer": ["重い"]},
    {"question":"밝다", "answer": ["明るい"]},
    {"question":"빠르다", "answer": ["速い"]},
    {"question":"알맞다", "answer": ["適当な/合う"]},
    {"question":"시작하다", "answer": ["始める"]},
    {"question":"약속하다", "answer": ["約束する"]},
    {"question":"운동하다", "answer": ["運動する"]},
    {"question":"걱정하다", "answer": ["心配する"]},
    {"question":"계산하다", "answer": ["計算する"]},
    {"question":"찾다", "answer": ["探す"]},
    {"question":"팔다", "answer": ["売る"]},
    {"question":"그리다", "answer": ["描く"]},
    {"question":"끄다", "answer": ["消す"]},
    {"question":"나누다", "answer": ["分ける"]},
    {"question":"남기다", "answer": ["残す"]},
    {"question":"넘다", "answer": ["越える"]},
    {"question":"늘다", "answer": ["伸びる"]},
    {"question":"닦다", "answer": ["磨く"]},
    {"question":"달리다", "answer": ["走る"]},
    {"question":"돌다", "answer": ["回る"]},
    {"question":"드리다", "answer": ["差し上げる"]},
    {"question":"들다", "answer": ["入る "]},
    {"question":"떠나가다", "answer": ["立ち去る"]},
    {"question":"식사하다", "answer": ["食事する"]},
    {"question":"요리하다", "answer": ["料理する"]},
    {"question":"전화하다", "answer": ["電話する"]},
    {"question":"결정하다", "answer": ["決定する"]},
    {"question":"찍다", "answer": ["(写真を)撮る"]},
    {"question":"타다", "answer": ["乗る"]},
    {"question":"걷다", "answer": ["歩く"]},
    {"question":"꾸다", "answer": ["(夢を)見る"]},
    {"question":"끝내다", "answer": ["終える"]},
    {"question":"나타나다", "answer": ["現れる"]},
    {"question":"낫다", "answer": ["治る"]},
    {"question":"느끼다", "answer": ["感じる"]},
    {"question":"다치다", "answer": ["怪我をする"]},
    {"question":"달라지다", "answer": ["変わる"]},
    {"question":"던지다", "answer": ["投げる"]},
    {"question":"돌려주다", "answer": ["返す"]},
    {"question":"듣다", "answer": ["聞く"]},
    {"question":"들리다", "answer": ["聞こえる"]},
    {"question":"뛰다", "answer": ["走る"]},
    {"question":"마치다", "answer": ["終わる"]},
    {"question":"맡다", "answer": ["引き受ける"]},
    {"question":"계획하다", "answer": ["計画する"]},
    {"question":"대신하다", "answer": ["代わりにする"]},
    {"question":"말씀하다", "answer": ["お話しする"]},
    {"question":"번역하다", "answer": ["翻訳する"]},
    {"question":"모으다", "answer": ["集める"]},
    {"question":"묻다", "answer": ["尋ねる"]},
    {"question":"맞추다", "answer": ["合わせる"]},
    {"question":"계속하다", "answer": ["継続する"]},
    {"question":"대답하다", "answer": ["答える"]},
    {"question":"도착하다", "answer": ["到着する"]},
    {"question":"발표하다", "answer": ["発表とする"]},
    {"question":"부탁하다", "answer": ["依頼する"]},
    {"question":"모자라다", "answer": ["足りない"]},
    {"question":"바꾸다", "answer": ["代える"]},
    {"question":"그냥", "answer": ["そのまま/ただ"]},
    {"question":"그래도", "answer": ["それでも"]},
    {"question":"그러니까", "answer": ["だから"]},
    {"question":"그런데", "answer": ["ところで"]},
    {"question":"늘", "answer": ["いつも"]},
    {"question":"매우", "answer": ["非常に"]},
    {"question":"반드시", "answer": ["必ず"]},
    {"question":"보다", "answer": ["〜より"]},
    {"question":"그대로", "answer": ["そのまま"]},
    {"question":"그래서", "answer": ["それで"]},
    {"question":"그러면", "answer": ["それなら"]},
    {"question":"꼭", "answer": ["必ず"]},
    {"question":"또는", "answer": ["または"]},
    {"question":"바로", "answer": ["正しく/すぐに"]},
    {"question":"벌써", "answer": ["すでに"]},
    {"question":"아마", "answer": ["たぶん"]}
  ]
}
